{
    "subject": "resource/Sarah_Silverman",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Sarah Silverman was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9235058426856995,
            "question": "Is Sarah Silverman American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8987383246421814,
            "question": "Where was Sarah Silverman born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7743018865585327,
            "question": "Which country is associated with Sarah Silverman's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7154309749603271,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Sarah Silverman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7040810585021973,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Sarah Silverman's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6847631931304932,
            "question": "Is the United States considered Sarah Silverman's home country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6736181974411011,
            "question": "What is Sarah Silverman's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6012484431266785,
            "question": "What country is Sarah Silverman from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44376495480537415,
            "question": "In what nation did Sarah Silverman come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38150739669799805,
            "question": "Where did Sarah Silverman spend her early years?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sarah Silverman was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7571_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what nation did Sarah Silverman come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7571_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Sarah Silverman from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7571_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sarah Silverman's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7571_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7571_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7571/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt contains the following sentence:\n\n\"She has received numerous awards and accolades throughout her career, including a Primetime Emmy Award and two Screen Actors Guild Awards.\"\n\nThis supports the triple that Sarah Silverman is an author of some sort (comedic writings), but more importantly, it mentions that she was born in the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Sarah Silverman was born on December 1, 1970, in Bedford, New Hampshire, which is in the United States. Therefore, the statement \"Sarah Silverman was born in the United States\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}